

Bruno R. R. Pereira

MOBILE DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

4+ years of experience in the field of mobile development, using Kotlin and Java for developing Android apps, Swift for IOS apps and Flutter/Dart for multi-plataform apps. I'm currently working for one brazilian's main banks (Banco Itaú) with the bank's main mobile app. I work with code versioning through Git, integrated and unit tests and use of Jira. I have a bachelor's degree in systems analysis and I'm fluent in English and Spanish (also my native language is portuguese).

Portfolio: https://brunorrp13.github.io

Github: https://github.com/brunorrp13

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/bruno -r-b0775b15a

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address

Passo Fundo, RS - Brazil

CONTACT

brunorrp13@hotmail.com



WORK EXPERIENCE

Mobile Developer

ITAÚ UNIBANCO

11/2021 - Present

- Development and maintenance of the banks native Android and IOS apps (with Kotlin, Java and Swift) and cross-platform apps with Flutter (Dart), using the bloc pattern, MVVM standard, SOLID principles, unit testing, dependency injection, Firebase, Jetpack Compose, Clean Architecture, API integration with Retrofit, Room, dependency injection with Koin, Git for code versioning and tools such as Jira for task control. Constant collaboration with the productand design teams (UI/UX). Expertise in application coverage and development of unit and integration tests. Support for features, fixes and any failures, solving business problems.

Mobile Developer

DELIVERY CENTER

07/2021 - 11/2021

 Agile development of the company's Android and IOS application in Java, Kotlin and Swift using Firebase for feature flags and crash reports, dependency injection with Dagger Hilt, Mix Pannel and New Relic for metrics, Azure for database visualization and Github for code versioning.

MOBILE DEVELOPER JR.

ATLAS COPCO BRASIL

02/2019 - 07/2021

- Maintenance of companies mobile apps in Flutter (Dart) using the bloc pattern, unit tests, widget implementations amongst other tasks.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree in Systems Analysis

UNIVERSIDADE CRUZEIRO DO SUL

2019-2021

Bachelor's degree in Administration

UNIVERSIDADE SÃO JUDAS TADEU

2008-2011